▍2026 国家银行公开赛（蒙特利尔）决赛
谢尔顿 6-3 7-6(4) 中岛布兰登 · 赛后捧杯致辞
Well, uh, uh, first of all,
首先
and most importantly, I want to thank God.
也是最重要的 我要感谢上帝
Um, I would be nowhere without my faith.
没有信仰 就没有今天的我
Uh, that's what's most important to me.
这对我来说是最重要的
So, I want to congratulate Brandon.
我要恭喜布兰登
Um, first of all, hell of a speech.
首先 刚才那番话说得真棒
Uh but no, seriously, to see the the way
说真的 看到你这一周
that you played this week, um the way
打出来的表现
that you've been playing, I know
还有你最近这段时间的状态
that people here may not have been tuned
这里的观众可能没关注
into DC last week, but uh to see the level
上周的华盛顿站
that you were playing there,
但看到你在那儿的水准
uh to see the work that you and your team
看到你和团队下的功夫
have been putting in and uh your evolution
还有你作为球员的成长
as a player has been so cool.
都特别酷
Um you are the the the future
你代表着未来
of American tennis.
美国网球的未来
we all are and it's so cool
我们都是 而且很酷的是
to be on this journey with you.
能和你一起走这一路
So, uh, congrats on this week and seriously,
所以 恭喜你这一周
good luck the rest of this season.
也祝你这个赛季接下来顺利
I want to thank my team.
我要感谢我的团队
Uh, it's crazy that we were here a year ago.
很神奇 一年前我们也在这儿
Um, well, I guess in Toronto.
呃 好吧 那是在多伦多
Uh, I I'm not going to say anything bad
我可不会说
about Toronto.
多伦多的坏话
I I love Toronto, too.
我也很爱多伦多
Um, but Montreal just as much.
但蒙特利尔我一样爱
Uh, you guys have paved the way for me,
你们为我铺好了路
made everything possible.
让这一切成为可能
Um, the team that I have around me
我身边的这个团队
is amazing.
了不起
Uh, FedE, you've been such a great addition
费德 你加入这个团队
to this team.
太棒了
and uh you're the only person here
你是现在我这个包厢里
in my box right now that's not family.
唯一一个不是家人的人
So uh I appreciate uh your commitment
谢谢你为我这么尽心
to me.
我很感激
Uh this has been a fun ride
这一路很尽兴
and we're only getting started.
而我们才刚刚开始
But to my family, you guys have been there
还有我的家人 你们始终陪着我
since since the beginning
从最开始就是这样
and uh always supported me.
一直支持着我
My uncle, he'll fly to Australia to see me.
我叔叔会飞去澳大利亚看我
And uh I don't know how many uncles
我不知道有几个叔叔
will do that.
会这么干
So, uh, to my parents, Uncle Rick,
所以 我的父母 里克叔叔
I appreciate you guys.
我很感激你们
Love you guys.
爱你们
Uh, to the sponsors, uh, National Bank,
还有赞助商 国家银行
Rogers, uh, to Tennis Canada,
罗渣士 加拿大网球协会
everyone who makes this event possible.
每一个让这站赛事办起来的人
It's a outstanding event.
这是一站出色的赛事
Uh it's run so well
办得非常好
and a lot of people don't see the behind
很多人看不到
the scenes work, but I appreciate you guys.
幕后的付出 但我很感激你们
All the volunteers, the drivers,
所有志愿者 司机
the ball kids, uh the stringers,
球童 穿线师
uh the people at the practice desk,
练习场登记台的工作人员
the umpires, uh tour managers, uh press,
裁判 巡回赛主管 媒体
um the list goes on and on.
还能一直数下去
But um this is a a big operation uh
这是一个庞大的运转
a serious serious event and to be a part
一站非常正式的赛事
of it is is an honor.
能参与其中是我的荣幸
So thank all of you.
谢谢你们所有人
Last of all, I want to thank the fans.
最后 我要感谢球迷
Uh Tennis wise, this has been one
从网球本身来说
of the best weeks of my life.
这是我人生中最好的一周之一
Um, I've played some of the best tennis
我打出了我这辈子
that I've ever played, and to be able to put
最好的一些网球
that uh on display here in front of you, um,
能在你们面前展现出来
has been an honor.
是我的荣幸
So, thank you guys
所以 谢谢你们
for bringing the energy all week.
这一整周带来的热情
I I love this game.
我热爱这项运动
Uh, I love competing
我热爱竞争
and uh I may not win every time I play,
我不一定每场都能赢
but I always leave it all on the court.
但我总会把一切都留在场上
Uh, I definitely left some skin
今天我肯定在那半边场地上
and blood on that side of the court.
留下了几块皮和几滴血
Um, but that'll always be the case for me.
但我一直都是这样
So, thank you guys so much.
所以 太谢谢你们了